## Luiz Bossetto

 ♥ Bloomington, Illinois
 ■ luiz.fbossetto@outlook.com
 € (309) 856-0506
 in Luiz Bossetto
 © luizfboss

## **PROFILE**

A passionate, self-driven, and creative Computer Science student. Possess excellent technological expertise, well-developed communication skills, and the essential ability to perform well in a team. Aim to expand my knowledge, learn from experienced team members, and help others through what technology can offer.

## **EDUCATION**

Illinois Wesleyan University

Bloomington, IL

Pursuing a Bachelor of Arts - August 2022, Present

• Major: Computer Science

Colegio Singular

Santo André, Brazil

High School - January 2019, December 2021

**TECHNICAL SKILLS** 

HTML CSS Microsoft Excel Adobe Illustrator

+ Bootstrap

JavaScript Python SQL

+ReactJS **C++** 

**WORK EXPERIENCE** 

Web Designer 01/2022 – 05/2022

Freelancer Brazil

Developed websites for local businesses, increasing brand exposure and improving

revenue.

**Coding Mentor** 08/2021 – 09/2021

Grow&Share Brazil

In charge of teaching coding skills to high school students whose school does not offer

Coding classes.

Student Worker 09/2022 – Present

Sodexo - Illinois Wesleyan University Bloomington, Illinois

Prepare and cook food ensuring the highest quality service and experience for customers (students and faculty).

(2000001100 01100 1000010))

**LANGUAGES** 

English Portuguese

Fluent. TOEFL Certification Native Speaker

**COURSES** 

Mastering Web Development 2022 – Present

Faus

Introduction to Quantum Computing 2021 – 2022

IBM & QubitXQubit

Introduction to JavaScript 2021

Google & Curso Em Video

Python - From Basic to Advanced 2021

Geek University

CS50 - Introduction to Computer Science 2020 – 2021

Harvard

Motion Design and Game Development 2018 – 2021

School of Art, Games, and Animation